{"results": [
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "In 'The Little Mermaid,' who is NOT one of Triton’s daughter?",
        "answer": "Adora",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Andrina",
            "Attina",
            "Alana"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "Which phrase does the Evil Queen in 'Snow White' actually say?",
        "answer": "Magic mirror, on the wall — who is the fairest one of all?",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Mirror, mirror, on the wall — who is the fairest of them all?",
            "Mirror, mirror, on the wall — who is the fairest one of all?",
            "Magic mirror, on the wall — who is the fairest of them all?"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "In the movie 'Tangled,' Flynn Rider is wanted dead or alive according to his wanted poster because he's a...",
        "answer": "Thief",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Bandit",
            "Treasonist",
            "Robber"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "In 'Sleeping Beauty,' what is the name of Maleficent’s pet raven?",
        "answer": "Diablo",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Malum",
            "Mauvais",
            "Diable"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "Finish the lyrics: 'Wouldn't you think I'm the girl, the girl who has everything? Look at this trove, treasures untold…'",
        "answer": "How many wonders can one cavern hold?",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "It’s full of gizmos and gadgets galore.",
            "Wonders from all over the world.",
            "There so much to be known."
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "In 'Frozen,' how many brothers does Hans have?",
        "answer": "12",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "7",
            "9",
            "15"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "In 'Pocahontas,' what did Pocahontas see in her dream that made her believe that a change was coming?",
        "answer": "A spinning arrow",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "A strange cloud formation",
            "A hawk circling her village",
            "A burning blue fire"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "Finish the lyrics: 'My soul is spiraling in frozen fractals all around…'",
        "answer": "And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "That wraps my heart in a cold and distant past.",
            "Somehow I’ve now been given a new chance.",
            "And all my problems are far gone in the past."
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "In 'Sleeping Beauty,' what do the fairies arm Prince Phillip with to fight Maleficent?",
        "answer": "Sword of Truth and Shield of Virtue",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Sword of Destiny and Shield of Bravery",
            "Sword of Righteousness and Shield of Honor",
            "Sword of Valiantness and Shield of Triumph"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "In 'Aladdin,' what does Aladdin, and a reluctant Abu, give to the poor children to eat?",
        "answer": "Bread",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Dates",
            "Apples",
            "Cheese"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "What is the name of the organization Bernard and Miss Bianca work in 'The Rescuers'?",
        "answer": "The Rescue Aid Society",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "The International Rescue Organization",
            "The Rescuers",
            "The Secret Helpers"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "In 'Beauty and the Beast,' how many eggs does Gaston say he eats in order to stay 'roughly the size of barge'?",
        "answer": "Five dozen",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Four Dozen",
            "Nine Dozen",
            "Seven Dozen"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "In 'Princess and the Frog,' what fictional country is Prince Naveen from?",
        "answer": "Maldonia",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Maramorgos",
            "Mypos",
            "Mrač"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "In 'Hercules,' Hades promised not to harm Megara if Hercules gave up his strength for how long?",
        "answer": "24 hours",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "12 hours",
            "36 hours",
            "48 hours"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "On whose shoulders does Dopey stand on in order to dance with Snow White during 'The Silly Song' scene?",
        "answer": "Sneezy",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Doc",
            "Grumpy",
            "Happy"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "In 'Alice in Wonderland,' aside from a pocket watch, what else is the White Rabbit holding when Alice encounters him?",
        "answer": "An umbrella",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "A cane",
            "A top hat",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How many years does the Genie say he has been trapped in the lamp?",
        "answer": "10,000 years",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "100 years",
            "500 years",
            "1,000 years"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "In 'The Sword in the Stone,' what is the name of Merlin’s pet owl?",
        "answer": "Archimedes",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Aristotle",
            "Socrates",
            "Plato"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "In 'Lady and the Tramp,' Jim Dear gives his wife Darling, Lady as a gift for…",
        "answer": "Christmas",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Valentine's Day",
            "Her Birthday",
            "For their Anniversary"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "In 'The Little Mermaid,' what alias does Ursula use when she becomes human?",
        "answer": "Vanessa",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Alexis",
            "Sonia",
            "Amber"
        ]
    }
]}